I want to publicly thank Amanda Seals.
And I want to thank her because in the last like 24 hours, thousands of you have started
to follow me all over social media.
You're on TikTok and I've only been on TikTok in the last like three days.
You're pre-ordering my book.
There's all these DMs that I'm getting of you telling me your stories of struggling
with capitalism.
And so I want to thank her for stirring up this conversation that's really important
to me.
And in many ways, it felt like many of you were not checking for that conversation.
Y'all weren't trying to talk about liberation.
Y'all weren't trying to talk about Palestine.
I could post something and there was no engagement or people would send me private messages because
they didn't feel like they could publicly post about these issues.
So one, I got to thank her because with her 2 million followers and so much to lose, as
many of us do, like I have a lot to lose by constantly talking about Palestine as I'm
releasing a book.
I thank her for not allowing profit to matter more to her than people.